

b'TSSE'
b'Lame3.99'


b'TIT2'
b'Newly tagged'


b'TCON'
b'Pop'


b'TRCK'
b'02/12'


b'TALB'
b'A Head Full Of Dreams'


b'USLT::eng'
b"The birds, they sang at break of day\nStart again, I hear them say\nIt's so hard to just walk away\n\nThe birds, they sang all the choir\nStart again, a little higher\nIt's a spark in a sea of gray\n\nThe sky is blue\nDreamed out loud till it's true\nThen taken back the part\nShine through\n\nMy arms turn wings\nOh, those clumsy things\nSend me up to that wonderful world\nAnd then I'm up with the birds\n\nMight have to go where they don't know my name\nFloat all over the world just to see her again\nAnd I won't show a fear, any pain\nEven though all my armor might rust in the rain\n\nA simple plot but I know one day\nGood things are coming our way\nA simple plot but I know one thing\nGood things are coming our way\n\nOh yeah"


b'TPE1'
b'Coldplay'


b'TDRC'
b'2015'


b'TPUB'
b'Parlophone Label Group (Plg)'
